{
    "subject": "resource/Matthew_McDonough",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedBand",
    "object": "resource/Mudvayne",
    "human_readable": "Matthew McDonough is associated with Mudvayne.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9846944212913513,
            "question": "Is Matthew McDonough a member of Mudvayne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7394654154777527,
            "question": "Who is associated with the band Mudvayne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6454277634620667,
            "question": "What is the name of the band that Matthew McDonough is associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5271202921867371,
            "question": "Is Matthew McDonough involved in music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4709463119506836,
            "question": "Can you name a musician connected to Mudvayne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31446462869644165,
            "question": "Who plays in the band Mudvayne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28339195251464844,
            "question": "What band might Matthew McDonough be a part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2815624177455902,
            "question": "To which musical group does Matthew McDonough belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27381381392478943,
            "question": "What band is Matthew McDonough known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2556179463863373,
            "question": "What is Matthew McDonough's musical affiliation?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Matthew McDonough is associated with Mudvayne.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2976_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What band is Matthew McDonough known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2976_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which musical group does Matthew McDonough belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2976_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What band might Matthew McDonough be a part of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2976_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2976_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2976_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2976_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2976_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2976_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2976_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2976_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2976_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2976_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2976_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Matthew McDonough is associated with Mudvayne. The documents mention that Matthew McDonough is the drummer for heavy metal band Mudvayne, and has appeared and performed on every release by Mudvayne."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references that Matthew McDonough is indeed associated with the heavy metal band Mudvayne, confirming the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}